musichostnetwork.com 2012-12-30

# Music Host Network Digital music distribution for independent artist. | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We want you to know that we value your privacy, accordingly we have set out this policy that states clearly how we use and store personal information.

IMPORTANT: BY USING THIS WEBSITE YOU GIVE YOUR CONSENT THAT ALL PERSONAL DATA SUBMITTED BY YOU MAY BE PROCESSED BY US FOR THE PURPOSES SET OUT BELOW

**1\. COMPLIANCE**  
We comply with the United Kingdom Data Protection Act 1998. To access current Data Protection legislation materials, click [here](http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk/).

**2\. PRIVACY**  
We take care to protect the privacy of our customers. This policy explains how we process information about website visitors and those registered with us.

**3\. WEBSITE DATA COLLECTION**  
Personal information is collated and stored primarily during the registration process, but is also monitored when there is activity on your account and when you use the website. As with many other websites, we may use software known as 'cookies' to store information relating to your preferences to enable us to improve our service to you.

**4\. YOUR PERSONAL DATA**  
Personal data submitted by you to this website will be used for the following purposes only. We will only collect and retain personal data to the extent that it is strictly necessary for our purposes. These purposes are; To assist us in setting up and managing your account. To build up an accurate customer profile of you, in order to make available to you promotional or relevant information from us;

If you have registered with this website and do not wish to receive promotional or relevant information then please "Login", and "Update your details" to opt out.

**5\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA**  
Personal data which we collect about you when you visit this site will be disclosed only to the following types of persons:

a). Any company or other entity to whom we may sell all or part of our business;

b). Any competent legal, regulatory or law enforcement authority. In the latter case, you will not be informed of any disclosure nor of any reasons for such disclosure and you hereby waive any and all rights that you may have, whether at law or otherwise, of any nature and in any jurisdiction, in connection with such disclosure;

c). Our professional advisers or other appropriate third parties, if your use of our service or this website is in breach of these terms and conditions.

**6\. DATA ACCESS & CORRECTIONS**  
Upon receipt of your written request which should be addressed to The Data Protection Officer, we will disclose to you your personal data held by us, we shall correct or delete inaccurate details. Changes to certain parts of your account information can also be made by accessing "Login" and checking "Update your details". We regularly delete data which is no longer required.

**7\. TRANS-BORDER DATA TRANSFERS**  
No transfers of your personal data are currently made outside of the European Economic Area. However, we reserve the right to relocate our web servers to a secure location outside the EEA in the future. If we do this, we will enter into agreements requiring the guardians of your personal data to adhere to standards of data protection substantially similar to those prevailing in the European Economic Area. However, the Internet is made up of a large variety of international connections and if you are visiting this website the various communications may well result in the temporary transfer of information outside the European Economic Area other than pursuant to contractual arrangements made by us. By visiting the website and communicating electronically with us you consent to these transfers.

**8\. GOOGLE ADVERTISING COOKIE**  

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html). 

**9\. GOVERNING LAW AND DISPUTES**  
This policy and consent forms part of our website terms of use and as such it shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of England and Wales. You irrevocably agree that the courts of England and Wales shall have exclusive jurisdiction to resolve any dispute or claim of whatever nature arising out of or relating to this policy and consent or otherwise to the use of your personal data, and that the laws of England and Wales shall govern such dispute or claim. However, we retain the right to bring legal proceedings in any jurisdiction where we believe that infringement of our intellectual property rights or breach of those terms is taking place or originating. You are responsible for compliance with any applicable laws and regulations of the jurisdiction from which you are accessing this website. We operate this website from England and make no representation or warranty that the information contained herein is appropriate or available for use in other locations outside England and Wales.

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy, please send your feedback using the contact system in the main window.

Close Window | Print this page
